Full Stack Developer Profile

OBJECTIVE

Detail-oriented problem solver with 460+ training hours and experience developing full stack applications. Interested in attaining a career that will allow the opportunity to excel in software development as well as utilize previous field experience and leadership abilities.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Java
- Javascript
- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- SQL
- Solid OOP Principles
- Git and Github
- Spring and Spring Boot
- Project Management
- Relationship Management
- Concept Design & Execution
- Technical Support
- Leadership & Development

SOFTWARE PROFICIENCIES

| Music Master | G Selector |
|------------------|----------------|
| Microsoft Office | Wide Orbit |
| NexGen | Adobe Creative |
| Voxpro | Replay 360 |
| Pro Tools | Soundforge |
| Prophet | Zetta |
| Audacity | Final Cut Pro |
| Logic Pro | Audition |
| Reaper | Mediabase |
| Playlist Editor | BDS |

TRAINING AND EDUCATION

Generation Developer Program | July 2022 - November 2022

- 17-Week Developer Bootcamp
- Learned technologies involved in creating full stack web apps
- Implemented unit tests and deployed the apps to Netlify and Heroku
- Tech Used: Java, Javascript, Spring and SpringBoot, Node.js, Git and Github

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

New Generation Radio | June 2021 to current

Evening Broadcast Host

- Enhance listener experience with strategic use of artist audio, listener discussions and news-related clips.
- Helped elevate station's market weight by increasing evening show rating by 15% where they consistently remain.

KBFB-FM Radio One Dallas | November 2012 – April 2021

Assistant Program Director/Music Director/Afternoon on-air host

- Managed and lead a team of 9 involved in executing various responsibilities daily.
- Continued elevating audience listening experience for audiences which resulted in 5% average ratings increase book over book.
- Cultivated and maintained strategic partnerships with label representatives to gain access to exclusive songs, artist interviews, and promotions.
- Scheduled daily music logs and coordinated weekly rotation changes by augmenting utilization of various industry software.
- Booked mix shows and specialty shows for air, and assisted in booking artist showcases and exclusive album-listening sessions.

KKFR-FM, Riviera, Phoenix | June 2010 - May 2012 Morning Show Host

- Co-hosted daily morning show, discussed engaging topics, wrote scripts and organized fundraising and community events.
- Bolstered morning show ratings increasing the price per unit for advertising slots by 10% resulting in overall revenue growth.
- Strengthened brand awareness by arranging community gatherings, including entertainment and meet-and-greet events.
- Advocated for corporate social responsibility by coordinating charity event planning to raise funds for multiple causes.

WebDevJesse@yahoo.com • 602-614-3053 • LinkedIn • Plano, TX, 75093